{
    "subject": "resource/The_Rock_Star_and_the_Mullahs",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Rock Star and the Mullahs is a film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8888775110244751,
            "question": "What might be some themes explored in a film called 'The Rock Star and the Mullahs'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7863414287567139,
            "question": "Is 'The Rock Star and the Mullahs' a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6582333445549011,
            "question": "What type of work is 'The Rock Star and the Mullahs'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1727147102355957,
            "question": "Who might be the main characters in this film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14352324604988098,
            "question": "What kind of music might be featured in this film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0810425728559494,
            "question": "Would you be interested in watching this film? Why or why not?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07598738372325897,
            "question": "Where do you think this film is set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05417529121041298,
            "question": "What challenges might the characters face in this film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.036704063415527344,
            "question": "Can you imagine any real-life events that inspired this film title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.036507826298475266,
            "question": "What kind of message do you think the filmmakers are trying to convey with this title?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Rock Star and the Mullahs is a film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6560_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you imagine any real-life events that inspired this film title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6560_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What challenges might the characters face in this film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6560_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where do you think this film is set?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6560_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6560_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents describe \"The Rock Star and the Mullahs\" as a documentary, which supports the statement that it is a film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}